Here's the correct answer.
这是正确答案
And the complete documentation for abs.
是 abs 的完整文档
You could have even look this up on Java's documentation web page.
你可以在 Java 文档的网页页面查到这个文档
This documentation includes a general description of what this absolute value function
这个文档包括绝对值函数的一般描述
does and it includes a description of the return value, just like before.
还包括返回值的描述
But the previous documentation for abs was missing
但是之前 abs 文档缺少
this parameters section and that's an important part of this function.
参数部分 而参数是这个函数的重要部分
Abs takes in one parameter an int,
abs 包括一个 int 参数
named a, that it calculates the absolute value of.
名字为 a 可以计算绝对值
So the correct answer is that
所以正确答案是
this documentation was missing a description of its parameter a,
这个文档缺少参数 a 的描述
and to include that in a Java doc comment it would look like this,
为了把它写入 Java doc 注释中
an at symbol followed by param,
应该在 param 前面加上符号 @
then the name of that parameter,
和参数名
which is just the letter A.
即字母 a
And then finally a description of that parameter.
然后最后是对这个参数的描述
Again, we already had a return value description so we
我们已经有了返回值的描述
don't need to add this return part of the Java doc comment.
所以我们不需要在 Java doc 注释中增加返回描述部分
And this last parameter comment line is incomplete,
最后参数注释行并不完整
because it doesn't include the name of that parameter, the name A.
因为它没有包含参数名 即字母 a
So @param a, the argument whose absolute value is to be determined,
所以 @param a, the argument whose absolute value is to be determined
is the correct answer.
是正确答案
So if we include this parameter description line,
如果我们加入这个参数描述行
the complete Java doc comment that goes along with
文档中完整的 Java doc
this documentation looks like this: First,
应当是这样 首先
a general description that tells us what the function abs does.
一般性描述告诉我们函数 abs 是什么
It returns the absolute value of a given int.
它可以返回给定整数的绝对值
Next, are parameters.
然后是参数
In this case there's one parameter, parameter A.
在这个例子中只有一个参数 即参数 a
And to describe that in a comment,
为了在注释中描述参数
we say @param a, then the description.
我们使用 @param a 再加上描述
And that was our correct answer.
这是我们的正确答案
And finally, we have our @return with the description of the return value.
最后我们用 @return 作为返回值的描述
And with this complete documentation,
通过这个完整的文档
we can figure out how to use this abs function by putting in
我们可以明白如何使用这个 abs 函数
a number and expecting a returned absolute value,
通过写入数字 得到返回的绝对值
even though we haven't seen this function before.
即使之前我们没见过这个函数
And that's what's so cool about documentation.
这就是文档的独特之处